I have big news to share. I'm back in
the US and this time it's a bit more
long-term.
After a long two and a half year
process, my husband finally got his
American green card.
It's a bit bittersweet because I'm very
excited to be back in my home country
and to see my family, but I was also
very sad leaving Korea. I love Korea and
I'm going to miss it very much, but it
makes me feel better knowing that I'll
visit very often. So, don't worry. I'll
be back soon. The week before coming to
the US was extremely busy. I
participated in a children's education
convention at COEX. It was my first time
ever doing something like that and it
was an incredible experience. It was
hard work and took a lot of preparation,
but I learned a lot and the best part
was I got to meet a lot of you. I was so
touched because a lot of you traveled
from far away to meet us. Some of you
even brought gifts and I'm just so
grateful for each and every one of you.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Something that really inspired me was
how diverse our subscribers are. I met a
70-year-old woman, a high school boy,
and a bunch of young kids that are
watching my videos and using my
materials to study. It was truly amazing
and you all just inspire me so much.
After the convention, we traveled back
to Busan and had to move out of our
apartment. It was really exhausting
because we only had like 2 days to pack.
We had to sell and get rid of a bunch of
stuff and pack 10 years of our lives
into six suitcases. It was not easy. A
few days before our flight, we stayed
with my in-laws. They helped us out a
lot. So, Mom and Dad, if you're watching
this, thank you so much. You saved us.
We finished up a lot of last-minute
errands at their house, ate a lot of
delicious homemade Korean food, and just
spent some good quality time together.
We even got to celebrate the cameraman's
birthday together. We went out for
dinner with the whole family, had
birthday cake, and watched two movies in
1 day. We watched The Odyssey and the
new Spider-Man movie. Both of the movies
were really good, so I recommend
watching either of them. Actually,
[music] my last few days in Korea were a
little bit emotional for me. I first
[music] went to Korea in 2015
and didn't expect [music] to stay there
as long as I did. Over the years, I met
so many incredible people [music] and
made lots of happy memories. I feel so
lucky because [music] I traveled to a
lot of different cities all over the
country. [music] I traveled to Busan,
Jeju, Jeonju, Chuncheon, Ganghwado, and
I even made it to Ulleungdo. That was a
very [music] special experience and
something I'll never forget. I grew a
lot as a person throughout my years in
Korea and [music]
the people there impacted me the most. I
met some of my closest friends [music]
ever while living in Korea. I even cried
on [music] the phone at the airport
while talking to my friend Da-ho. She
called to say goodbye [music] and I just
lost it. Korea is such a beautiful
country and will always have a special
[music] place in my heart.
I'm [snorts] currently at my dad's
house. I'm going to be his roommate for
the next few months until I get settled
here in the US. I talked him into making
more content with me, so keep an eye out
for our upcoming videos together. Also,
tomorrow I leave for a very exciting
adventure. I'm going on an Alaskan
cruise with 12 other family members.
It's going to be a little bit chaotic,
but it's going to be a blast. And I'll
be filming the whole time, so stay
tuned. Until then, I'm going to just try
to get over this jet lag. I hope you're
all doing well, staying cool, [music]
and enjoying summer. I'll see you next
time. Bye.